I'm a short form content creator.
Seventy five percent of my revenue comes from brand sponsorships.
So you review products.
Yeah, more faceless as well.
So it's like not really a personal brand type of thing.
Cool. I'm realizing the current business model isn't as like scalable.
Why is it not scalable?
It's just I think like a little part of it's like unfulfilling.
And a lot of it is like, all right, I'm going to pause you right there
because I think this is really valuable.
Yeah, I hear that sentence all the time.
I have this business. It's working.
I don't think it's scalable.
I should do a different business.
If we reframe this as I'm doing her business, it's working and now it's hard.
And so I'd like to do something easy.
Can you tell me something easy?
That's what I hear.
Anyways, please continue.
I appreciate that.
Since I review 50 products a month, there's only so many times
I could post a video about it.
There's so many products. Yeah.
I mean, basically, why is this not scalable?
Why can't you review 500 products a month?
It is a possibility.
And then another thing is just me getting in my head about creating
a bunch of me's who is just doing the same thing
because it's basically like a formula.
Right. Yeah. Let's do more of that.
Do more? Yeah. Sweet.
This is a good talk.